stonehearth.net 2019-06-07

# Privacy Policy – Stonehearth

#### **STONEHEARTH.NET PRIVACY POLICY**

Protecting your privacy and providing a great experience for you on Stonehearth.net is important to us. We created this Privacy Policy so that you are aware what information we collect on the site, how we use it, and with whom who we share it.

#### **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register to participate in the forum and gather data when you read, write, and evaluate the content shared there. We also collect information if you sign up for our newsletter or e-mail list.

When registering or signing up, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site without registering or signing up. Your e-mail address may require verification by an e-mail containing a unique link. If that link is visited, we know that you control the e-mail address.

When registered and posting in the forum, we record the IP address that the post originated from. We also may retain server logs that include the IP address of every request to our server.

#### **How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To keep you up to date about the game and other happenings at Radiant through our newsletter (due to debut in Summer 2014);
  * To personalize your experience — your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs;
  * To improve our site — we continually strive to improve our site offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you;
  * To improve customer service — your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs;
  * To send periodic emails — the email address you provide may be used to send you information (for example, notifications from the forum that you request about changes to topics or in response to your username), respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

#### **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

#### **Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you permit). These cookies enable the site to recognize your browser and, if you have a registered account, associate it with your registered account.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

#### **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our site, conducting our business, or servicing you, or entities that acquire us or that we merge with, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

#### **Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act and players under 13**

Our site, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13 without parental consent, except as permitted by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) or other applicable laws.

If you are under the age of 13, per the requirements of COPPA, you should not provide us with any personal information unless your parent has approved.

#### **Accessing and making changes to your information**

You have the right to know about the information that we hold about you. If you would like to know what information we are holding, you should contact us. If the information we hold about you is wrong, insufficient or irrelevant, then you have the right to make sure that it gets corrected or removed.

If personal information you provided to us changes, or if you no longer wish us to have it, you may correct, update, amend, or deactivate it by contacting us at support@radiant-entertainment.com or by mailing us at the address listed below.

#### **Online Privacy Policy only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our site and not to information collected offline.

#### **Your consent**

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

#### **Contact information**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy or our privacy practices, please contact us at the following e-mail or postal address:

contact@radiant-entertainment.com

Radiant Entertainment Privacy Manager

5150 El Camino Real

Suite D30

Los Altos, CA 94022

#### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

#### _This document was last updated January 28, 2016._
